https://www.bemedwise.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
BeMedWise places a high priority on protecting your privacy. The personal information collected from the visitors of BeMedWise.org, including their identity, remains confidential. This privacy policy was created in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our website users. This policy explains what types of information is collected by BeMedWise.org and how this information is used.
What Personally Identifiable Information is Collected
Individuals that sign up to receive BeMedWise’s
e-communications voluntarily provide us with contact information (such as name
and e-mail address). We may use this information for specific, limited
purposes. You may always “opt out,” either now or at any time in the
future, if you do not wish to receive our messages. You may do this by checking
off the “unsubscribe” feature on emailings, or by emailing BeMedWise
with any questions at info@BeMedWise.org. You may also email us to review
any personal information collected to request corrections. We will endeavor to
respond to your email within two business days upon receiving it.
IP addresses
BeMedWise uses your IP address to help
diagnose problems with our server, to administer www.BeMedWise.org, and
for statistical metrics used to track website visitor traffic.
Google Analytics
Currently we are using Google Analytics to
analyze the audience of the website and improve our content. No personal
information is collected from Google Analytics. For further information on the
privacy policy concerning Google Analytics, please go here.
Cookies
www.BeMedWise.org may use
“cookie” messages to automatically help provide better services. They
remind us who you are and your preferences for our website based on what you’ve
done and told us before. The “cookie” is placed in your computer and
is read when you come back to our website. Cookies let us take you to the information
and features you’re particularly interested in. They also let us track your
usage of www.BeMedWise.org, so we know which parts of our sites are most
popular. You can reject cookies or cancel them by instructing your Web browser
accordingly.
How Your Information May Be Used
We use your personal information to provide
you with personalized service; to send e-mail alerts to you; to answer your
requests; etc. You may choose to opt out at any time, which will cease all
communications from us. We may also use your information to track visitor of
our website. This lets us see which of our features are the most popular so we
can better serve our users’ needs. It also lets us provide aggregate data about
our traffic (not identifying you personally, but showing how many visitors used
which features, for example) to outside parties. The BeMedWise website
administrator and IT staff have access to this information.
Email Privacy
BeMedWise does not provide, sell, or rent
email addresses to anyone outside the organization. If that policy should
change in the future you will have the opportunity to indicate whether or not
we have your permission to share it.
External Links
Www.BeMedWise.org includes links to external
websites. These links do not fall under the www.BeMedWise.org domain, and BeMedWise
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external
websites. Your use of any linked website is solely at your own risk.
Modifications
We may amend this privacy policy from time to
time; please review it periodically. We maintain the option to modify this
privacy at any time by electronic notice posted on our website. Your continued
use of our website after the date that such notices are posted will be deemed
to be your agreement to the changed terms.
